Hello friends, today we will talk
about ICICI Lombard General Insurance. The other three companies we have are Cadbury
Life, SBI Life and ICICI
Prudential Life Insurance. Now,
regarding life insurance, for the first time
we will focus on general insurance, so we will
talk about its fundamental principles and technical aspects. And what are the sensitivities that are happening here,
right? And here we should
see such a possibility. And I would
not like to demonstrate that I had a very
popular
Abe Test in this topic. And here I did a very good
investment and earned returns on it. He is
my favorite 100% witness Sylvester.
And like yesterday we did a
live streaming on Friday, December 4, 2020.
So, it was very good here. It was very nice to
talk to you all. So,
we decided to plan a little. All the people
who were present,
together we decided that we will do a
live streaming every Friday at 9:30.
Whatever your
queries are, whatever your problems are, I will
try to call everyone and after
seeing the chat, when you people tell me, I have done it
friends, so please try to be present on 9th/3rd
Friday and we all
connect, then our interaction will remain a little,
without your 100 times, today we will
talk and Ardha Narishwar can come, let's move ahead,
so here I will talk, first of all
some conclusions have come out in Anwar report, there is a
general
insurance company, there is a lot of
motor insurance here, but it used to be that a
lot of this thing happens, right
and MP Balbir is very much in focus here,
so here you people should provide
maximum motor insurance cover to such people and this can be
subscribed, so many people, these
appointments cannot be made and here
click on continue, it runs around 100 percent, there
should be no interruption in this and do not do it, okay
Sudhir, if there is a situation, there may be some problem in the economy, it may get
delayed, but this
23.0 thing that happened will keep coming, correct
and  Here, number 13 is 25 percent of
health and personal accident coverage, so
you can say that there could be a little
diversification here.
If a platform is found, if someone
goes to the company, that there is such good
competition here and such good
premium valuation here, then
if this is removed, then people
start moving in that direction. If
you increase the facility a little in the low premium, then
subscribe here. We cannot guarantee
that you will subscribe. You should
not subscribe at all.
Home is on the left side near us, subscribe here.
You and I will subscribe here, but it
was in 2008, but this is not a problem.
Here I will talk about it, otherwise you should
subscribe. And here on the policy itself, there was a small
loss of 90 percent here on the
policy, and the number of policy
tested number policies is slightly
reduced here, so you people will not take this as a negative, you
can take this opportunity which can be
more beneficial for you and  In the
claim settlement, you will see
that it is quite good and here our
investment is given in the name of under management, so
here you can see that Sikandar Management has increased quite significantly, its strength has
increased significantly as per the season, which has been
immersed in 181 studies, which shows many
things and is very positive, and here
subscribe and all this should be skipped, so
here like what
is 1.5, people's cup idea,
reduce it a little and subscribe and if you subscribe here, then
this was, then according to that,
if you subscribe to this number as per the total, then
subscribe to the channel,
definitely subscribe here and the company should not
wake up for
half a minute, there is no problem in terms of
capital addition for long term investment,
and if we
talk about debt here, when 425 crores was
settled, it was a minimalist and here the debt
to equity ratio came out to be 0.07, so there is nothing wrong
here and the
accused acted very intelligently.  28.7 will be
quite a lot of turmeric accused and
if you look at the peer comparison here, then
according to General Insurance, IAS is a lot but a
lot of Rafi people will be seen among the tribal friends
and despite having a strong accused here, the number of
Pimp Revenue Inspector will be
very less, what does this mean, is it getting
good numbers on very cheap goods option
and New India
Insurance, we cannot focus on this
because your accused are very less and will
remain low like this, so three, if this
subscribe is Leaders of General Insurance
Custom,
Ajay, and here I will talk about everything else,
like the debt here, which is very
low, so we have to keep it here only, but the
return on equity is
quite good at 20.98 and the place percentage is
not a problem, which is Crore 151, if
we subscribe more, then we
should not have any problem in wishing
and here 36 crores is quite good and
10 last five years, which is
very good, that people
keep it, so no problem, if there is a little delay
here  People do
not subscribe to subscribe, it means
with the company, so it is very good to subscribe to
your channel, it is very good, Anup
Ashraf-ul-Haq will be visible here and when it is worth Rs 6547
crore, which has been done for advertising, there has been improvement in it,
some
technological changes have happened, for that he
can use profit loss coupon, if we talk about it, then here if
you are a student, then
after behaving a little bit, it will
look very good here and here I will do a little more here that till
further sure, it is very good, so
here according to this
you people should subscribe and here by clicking
on the subscribe button, then according to this, there is
a small very long addition in the date, there is a
break-up
after that bank account, there is
a good sharp decline here, so if you people should do a
little introduction in this decline for free, then you
can subscribe
and for 10 minutes, the decline here is very
big, but do a lot of it and if you do it
above this, then here and here
subscribe, subscribe, from here till here,
not subscribe  It is possible that people can have a lot of
expectations here, it means people can have a lot of expectations, they should have that
here and both are
fine, so here we should talk according to them, so there has been
a consultation here,
after that consultation,
you
can see the proper response to the problem here with surprise and father
long-term, the stop here can go very high,
almost here for the short term
you can go with a target of 60,
not much, that is your Rs.32, there is a fall but you
can see a shampoo jump of around ₹10 for 1603 ₹10 here and here
how the discussion on multiverse happened, it has
not been told here, in such a situation, it had
blood coming out, so if you had
subscribed here, then very good things,
subscription is definitely appropriate to get it,
but according to the situation, 100 appointed,
run a little away,
he told that more than 40 people
invest, so you people can get
good money return according to this show, a green scan family  Let's do it
and here I will
talk about the most reliable Patan
Patan and we call it so here we
need to pay attention 2030
subscribe and here it is searched that
breaks the accused then ghee
to the next level but here is a good thing, otherwise a
little bit of yoga here,
if you subscribe here, but subscribe till now,
Vijay Banave is in good duty pot,
so if we talk accordingly, then here already the
option of submit will be visible and here
if I zoom out a little, if it reaches its
top level then it is
very good,
if it runs a little above then you people can
get good returns, so half of this 1434 has been
crossed which is a very
good thing and here that is why I can
say with confidence that in this
you people can see
good money returns in short term and mid term loan top teams on the internet, a
mixture of divergence was done, nothing like Tiger has been
formed, so according to that
anyone  You won't be able to draw conclusions, and
that's why I haven't included it in the chart. Let's
talk about the relation, which
was 0.42, so
0.42 circulation profession, meaning a
little dependency on the soil will help, so
it will work and it will disappear, so this will also work,
but it can't be as much with less, a
little bit of
introduction means it will, but
not that much, the relation behind the letter
means now, but enjoy it, so when we do the
moment of soil on the prostate, it will be
better, okay, and here I will talk about the one
that leaves us confused, which
we shouldn't do,
which is the chart, so here
with Haqqani, you will
see a danger signal that it is rat cancer, okay, so start doing
this raid, and one is formed, it is formed on Friday,
Sagar is formed on Monday, so
we will see a decline here until we
are not in the office here and in Soldier, until the
overflow comes, you people will do 10  The
level I told you, it will jump, rather it will go
around it and after that it will
start its plan, then it will be difficult to stop you,
correct, so the trap is short term, a
little small fall here, here you
people have to make a straight line for this potato,
I told you regularly, it would be better to do the same meaningful work,
correct, and I will
talk about that as per the tweet,
here the offer board has taken them
like tomato, but there is
no setting signal here, so
according to that you people do not have any problem,
here you people have a good fault station and
expedition bar, instead of estimation coming out of my mouth,
you people can do the estimation,
okay, so I am talking about one month, it is
inside it, so according to that
no swelling will be taken out on you people, which will remain, I will
make big green colored
and according to this you used to get looted, everyone has to do the work,
forget your
pocket and stop for investing,
this is quite good, I can talk to you with confidence,
light so much stock time means
very less stock to go to office  If you get
digest long general insurance then it
depends on you people,
how do you press it, egg, gular
part growth stock portfolio depends on you,
so this was the
fundamental right of general insurance in districts, how did you
like it,
do tell me in the comments once, if you have any problem then
you people can ask me, there is
no problem, if life but is coming then
you people can talk like this, if you like it then
definitely like it,
what happens by liking is that
your people's recommendation of this video increases,
keep it more on YouTube channel, if you feel like then you
can share it with many people, the
bigger your family is, the better our
learning will increase because with increasing penis,
learning should be the dream, so keep taking
full
care of your family and
definitely do more for the next video, thank you, thank you so much